Preliminary guide to the Dr. William Johnston Mallory papers papers, 1892-1956 MS2335.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Dr. William Johnston Mallory papers
1892-1956
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Mallory, Walter
MS2335.UA
1.25 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains letters, diplomas and other documents about Dr. William Johnston Mallory, GWU faculty in the medical school.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: George Washington University materials and Personal materials
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use.
Mallory, William Johnston; Mallory, Walter
- George Washington University material, 1892-1956; Series 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Course/exam grades, correspondence, certificates, event programs, 1903-1954; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, correspondence, certificates, event programs, 1938-1948; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Records from Office of the President, addresses, correspondence, 1927-1940; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Personal material, 1892-1956; Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Commencement/graduation addresses (GWU and non-GWU), 1934-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commencement/graduation addresses (non-GWU), 1938-1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Geneology and employment records, 1892-1955; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Records and correspondence from Philippines, 1903-1907; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Documents of leave from Philippines, 1905-1906; (Box 3) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Army records (and Army Medical Library and Museum), 1917-1950; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - (1 of 2) Membership records from medical societies, 1915-1951; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - (2 of 2) Membership records from medical societies, 1934-1956; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Obituary, euology, late resume, 1938-1956; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)